Finding Aid for Marketing and Communications (University of Michigan) records, 1950-1999
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Visual Materials
  - Photographs
    - University of Michigan
      - Subject Files
        - Frieze Building (Box 3)
        - Geological Science (Box 3)
        - Institute of Genontology (Box 3)
        - Glee Club (Box 3)
        - Handicapped 1985 (Box 3)
        - Harlan Hatcher Graduate Library, 1978-c.1995 (Box 3)
        - Hill Auditorium (Box 3)
        - Highway Safety Research Institute 1965 (Box 3)
        - Historical (Box 3)
        - Honors Convocation 1984 (Box 3)
        - Hospital 1950s-1990s (Box 4)
        - Housing 1960s-1980s (Box 4)
        - Inauguration, President Duderstadt 1988 (Box 4)
        - School of Information 1980s (Box 4)
        - Jobs, 1960s-1970s (Box 4)
        - Kellogg Eye Center (Box 4)
        - Kelsey Museum of Archaeology (Box 4)
        - Lab Scenes 1982-1987 (Box 4)
        - Landmarks and Architectural Elements (Box 4)
        - Law Library 1985-1994 (Box 4)
        - Law School 1981-1993 (Box 4)
        - Libraries 1980s (Box 4)
        - Literature, Science, and the Arts Building (Box 4)
        - Medical Center (Box 4)
        - Medical School 1970s-1980s (Box 4)
        - Medical Scientist Training Program 1988 (Box 4)
        - Michigan Union 1987-1990 (Box 4)
        - Michigan Women's Group 1985 (Box 4)
        - Department of Microbiology and Immunology (Box 4)
        - Museum of Art (Box 4)
        - Music Camp (Box 4)
        - School of Music (Box 4)
        - School of Natural Resources and Environment (Box 4)
        - Naval Architecture (Box 4)
        - Near Eastern Studies (Box 4)
        - North Campus Commons (Box 4)
        - School of Nursing (Box 4)
        - Observatory (Box 4)
        - Department of Pathology 1982 (Box 4)
        - College of Pharmacy 1980s (Box 4)
        - Power Center (Box 4)
        - Presidents and Dignitaries
          - Hatcher, Harlan (Box 4)
          - Fleming, Robben (Box 4)
          - Shapiro, Harold (Box 4)
          - Duderstadt, James (Box 4)
          - Bollinger, Lee (Box 4)
          - Ford, Gerald (Box 4)
          - Carter, Jimmy (Box 4)
          - Bush, George (Box 4)
        - President's House (Box 4)
        - School of Public Health (Box 4)
        - Rackham School of Graduate Studies (Box 4)
        - Regents (Box 4)
        - Regents' Plaza (including The Cube sculpture) (Box 4)
        - Research 1980s (Box 4)
        - Residential College (Box 4)
        - Revelli Hall (Box 4)
        - Seventies (Box 4)
        - Shapiro Undergraduate Library (Box 5)
        - Sixties (Box 5)
        - Slide Program and Script 1997 (Box 5)
        - Institute for Social Research (Box 5)
        - School of Social Work (Box 5)
        - Shady Trails Speech and Hearing Camp (Box 5)
        - Sports (Box 5)
        - Stadium (Box 5)
        - Student Activities Building (Box 5)
        - Student Scenes
          - Classroom and Academic (Box 5)
          - Non-Classroom (Box 5)
        - Summer Scenes (Box 5)
        - Tappan Hall (Box 5)
        - Taubman Center (Box 5)
        - Telefund (Box 5)
        - Theatre/Drama (Box 5)
        - Towsley Center (Box 5)
        - Upjohn Center for Clinical Pharmacology (Box 5)
        - Winter Scenes (Box 5)
  - Videotapes
    The final visual material format is videotapes. It includes a group Business School interviews filmed in 1999. This raw footage, apparently intended for an unidentified promotional video, documents key Business School professors' opinions about the program, identifies their current and past studies, and has him or her describe the school's doctoral programs. The two other videotapes within the record group are finished products from Marketing Communications. The Center for the Education of Women promotional video, filmed in the late 1980s or early 1990s, describes the services and achievements of the program. The Michigan Engineer, a 1983 promotional recruiting video for the College of Engineering, includes commencement footage, student commentary, and an interview with James Duderstadt.
    - Business School Interviews, VHS 1999
      - Batra, Rajeev, Marketing (Box 5)
      - Hoetker, Glen (Box 5)
      - Kaul, Gaudam (Box 5)
      - Olson, Judy, Computer and Information Systems (Box 5)
      - Lafontaine, Francine, Business Economics (Box 5)
      - Lovejoy, Bill, Operations Management (Box 5)
      - Slemrod, Joel, Office of Tax Policy Research (Box 5)
      - Thackor, Anjan (Box 5)
      - White, Joe (Box 5)
    - Center for the Education of Women Promotional Video, VHS circa 1990 (Box 5)
    - The Michigan Engineer, College of Engineering Promotional Video, U-Matic, 1983 (Box 5)
Related Material
Researchers seeking additional information about Marketing Communications' predecessor should examine the University of Michigan University Publications finding aid located at the Bentley Historical Library. The record group consists of photographic images from 1950 to 1970. There is also some additional information regarding the Publication Office within the Vice President for Development record group.